[

](https://blocksite.co/)

[

](https://blocksite.co/)

* Product
    * * * **Get more info**

        * * 

                Try our desktop app and block on multiple browser at once

* Resources
    * * * **We are here to help**
                
        * * **Customers reviews**

                Find out why our customers love us

        * * 

                Try our desktop app and block on multiple browser at once

* Follow us
    
    [

    ](https://www.facebook.com/BlockSite.co/)[

    ](https://twitter.com/BlockSite_)[

    ](https://www.linkedin.com/company/blocksite/)[

    ](https://www.instagram.com/blocksite_official/)
    
    Available on

[

](https://blocksite.co/)

* Product
    * * * **Get more info**

        * * 

                Try our desktop app and block on multiple browser at once

* Resources
    * * * **We are here to help**
                
        * * **Customers reviews**

                Find out why our customers love us

        * * 

                Try our desktop app and block on multiple browser at once

* Follow us
    
    [

    ](https://www.facebook.com/BlockSite.co/)[

    ](https://twitter.com/BlockSite_)[

    ](https://www.linkedin.com/company/blocksite/)[

    ](https://www.instagram.com/blocksite_official/)
    
    Available on

[Home](https://blocksite.co/) » Privacy Policy Website and App

Privacy Policy for Website, Mobile App, and Desktop App
=======================================================

BlockSite privacy policy and data collection practices.

**BLOCKSITE**
-------------

**PRIVACY POLICY FOR WEBSITE, MOBILE APP, AND DESKTOP APP**

_\[Last updated: September 26, 2024\]_

### **INTRODUCTION**

This privacy policy (“**Privacy Policy**“) governs the data collection practices of BlockSite LP (“**BlockSite**”, “**us**”, “**we**” and “**our**”) when you use our BlockSite mobile apps, desktop app, browser extension (the **Apps**”) or our website, [www.blocksite.co](http://www.blocksite.co/) (the “**Website**”). Within this Privacy Policy, the BlockSite Apps and Website are referred to as our “**Services**”. This Privacy Policy contains important disclosures on how we collect, share, and use (together referred to as “**process**”) your information. If you are a resident of California, please refer to Section 13 below, which includes additional privacy information for California Residents, the categories of personal information we collect and your rights under California privacy laws. We encourage you to read the Privacy Policy carefully prior to using our Services.      

**QUICK REFERENCE GUIDE**

* This Privacy Policy provides you with information about:
* Personal Information We Collect
* How We Use Personal Information
* How We Share Personal Information
* Aggregate Data and Non-identifiable Data
* Cookies and Similar Technologies
* Analytics
* Your Information Collection Choices
* How We Protect and Store Your Personal Information
* User Rights
* Delete Data and Exercise Rights
* Use By Children
* Changes to this Policy
* How to Contact Us
* Additional Privacy Information for California Residents

1. **PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

We collect “Personal Information” and “Personal Data” as defined under applicable privacy laws (collectively, “**Personal Information**”) when you create an account or communicate with us.  We also collect certain persistent identifiers automatically when you use the Services. Personal Information does not include information that we de-identify or aggregate consistent with applicable law. 

**Personal Information We Collect Directly From You**

* **Contact Information.** We may collect your name, email          and related general contact information, including login and password information, when you set up an account with us.
* **Communications Information.** When you email, call, or otherwise communicate with us and with members of our team, we may collect and maintain a record of your contact details, communications, and our responses. We also maintain records of communications and information that you post on our social media channels and information you provide to us related to any customer support requests.
* **Financial Information.** When payments are required, we use third party payment processors to conduct payments in connection with the Services.       

**Personal Information We Collect Automatically Through the Services**

When you use our Services, we collect: 

* Web server log information that web browsers and servers make available, including:
    * Browser type;
    * Language preference;
    * Date and time of each visitor request; 
    * URLs;
    * Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, but note that we permanently delete the last portion of the IP address and hash the full IP address before storing it, thus preventing us from having the ability to use it to transmit any information to or otherwise identify your device;
* Data about your device, such as your screen resolution, operating system, device manufacturer and model, and language.
* Browsing activity and information regarding websites and content accessed such as ads displayed on sites you visit. 
* Data about your use of the App, including content viewed, features used and the dates and times of your interactions with the App.

     We use cookies and similar technologies to recognize you as you use or return to the Services so that we can understand how the Services are used, optimize user engagement and customize and enhance your experience.   

**Personal Information Collected from Third Parties**

We may also collect and receive certain Personal Information about you from third party sources, such as from affiliates, business partners operating systems and social media platforms, public databases, and service providers who provide services or perform functions on our behalf. In addition, we may collect the following Personal Information from third-party sources:

* **Integrated Service Information**. We may make available the ability for you to access, register for, sign up, or otherwise interact, engage, or connect with the Services through certain third-party features or integrated services. By accessing our Services via these third-party connections or integrated services, such as through your Google, Facebook, or Apple accounts, we may collect or obtain certain Personal Information about you related to your use of such third-party services. For example, we may collect information related to your account and profile, such as your name, username, email, profile picture, friend lists, public postings, and other similar information available on your profile. You should check your privacy settings on each integrated service to better understand how your Personal Information may be used, disclosed, or otherwise processed by these parties.
* **Transaction Information.** Information relating to payments from you and other details of products or services you have purchased from us using third party payment processors. 

**Permissions Requested.** We request permission to collect activity data and network traffic information, including browsing data, in order to block distractions before you even see them. Some of our features are supported by our affiliates’ technologies, and your personal data and browsing activity is shared with such affiliates to enable us to provide Blocksite and for market intelligence purposes. To access these permissions, you will need to explicitly enable them through an in-app permission or the mobile/browser extension settings. You may opt-out at any time through “Your Privacy Choices” within the settings menu. If you opt out, features that rely on these technologies will no longer work.

2. **HOW WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We use the Personal Information collected from you for the following purposes:

* **Operating Services and Providing Related Support.** To provide and operate our Website and Services, provide troubleshooting and technical support, and for similar service and support purposes. We process your Personal Information for this purpose for the performance of a contract we have with you      e.g., because you have agreed to our Terms of Service) or to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract with you or to meet our legitimate interest (     e.g., to support the proper functioning of our Services) in doing so. 
* **Analytics and Improvement.** To better understand how users access and use the Website and Apps. In this regard, we have a legitimate interest in understanding how our Services work and ensuring the necessary improvements.
* **Marketing, Advertising and Campaign Management.** We may disclose Personal Information to third-party ad network providers and/or traffic measurement services, who may use this data to improve and measure the effectiveness of our ads and those of third parties. Where required by applicable law, we may obtain your consent in order to send you targeted marketing. We also have a legitimate interest in marketing and advertising our Services and may not rely on your consent to the extent permitted by applicable law.
* **Security and Protection of Rights.** To protect the Services and our business operations; to protect our rights or those of our stakeholders; to prevent and detect fraud, unauthorized activities and access, and other misuse; conduct risk and security control and monitoring; where we believe necessary, to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety or legal rights of any person or third party, or violations of our Terms of Service. To maintain our facilities and infrastructure and undertake quality and safety assurance measures. We have a legitimate interest in securing our assets and protecting our rights. 
* **Compliance and Legal Process.** To comply with the law and our legal obligations and respond to the legal process and related legal proceedings. In this regard, we will process your Personal Information to comply with our legal obligations, and in our legitimate interest. 
* **Business Transfers.** To consider and implement mergers, acquisitions, reorganizations, and other business transactions, and to administer our general business, accounting, recordkeeping, and legal functions. Any such processing of your Personal Information will be in our legitimate interest. 

3. **HOW  WE SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION** 

We may disclose Personal Information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy to the following parties: 

* **Vendors and Service Providers.** We may disclose Personal Information we collect to our service providers, processors, and vendors who perform functions on our behalf to allow us to provide the Services. 
* **Affiliates.** We may disclose Personal Information we collect to our affiliates, who may use this Personal Information in connection with their market intelligence or analytics services and otherwise in accordance with the principles of this Privacy Policy.  
* **Third Party Platforms and Networks.**  We may disclose or make available Personal Information to third parties in support of our marketing, advertising, and campaign management. 
* **Business Partners.** If we, our affiliates, or subsidiaries are or may be acquired by, merged with, or invested in by another company, or if any of our assets are or may be transferred to another company, whether as part of a bankruptcy or insolvency proceeding or otherwise, we may transfer the information we have collected from you to the other company. We may also share certain Personal Information as necessary prior to the completion of such a transaction or corporate transactions such as financings or restructurings, to lenders, auditors, and third-party advisors, including attorneys and consultants, as part of due diligence or as necessary to plan for a transaction.
* **Others as permitted or required by applicable law.** We may disclose Personal Information to third parties to the extent permitted or required by applicable law. This may include regulators, government entities, and law enforcement. It may also include certain disclosures that we are required to make.
* **Security and protection of rights**. We may disclose your Personal Information when we believe it is appropriate to do so to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Use or this Privacy Policy, or as evidence in litigation in which we are involved.

We will take the necessary steps to ensure that international transfers of personal data (including Personal Information) meet all requirements under applicable data protection laws. When personal data collected within the European Economic Area (“**EEA**“) or the UK is transferred outside those markets, we will take the steps necessary to ensure that sufficient safeguards are provided to such data during its transfer and processing outside of the EEA or the UK. Some of the measures implemented to safeguard your Personal Information include ensuring that the recipient is bound by specific contractual clauses approved by the European Commission and / or the UK Government to provide adequate protection for Personal Information. Where applicable, you can request a copy of the relevant contractual safeguards that we have put in place.  

4. **AGGREGATED DATA AND NON-IDENTIFIABLE DATA**

We may use and disclose aggregated and other non-identifiable data related to our business and the Services for quality control, analytics, research,      development, and other purposes.      Some of this information may be considered “deidentified” under U.S. privacy laws (i.e., data that it is no longer linked or reasonably linkable to an identified or identifiable consumer). Where we rely on data that has been “de     identified” as defined by U.S. privacy laws, we will:  a           (i) take reasonable measures to ensure that the de-identified information cannot be associated with an individual, household, or device; (ii) commit to maintain and use the information in de-identified form and not attempt to re-identify the information; and (iii) contractually obligate any further recipient to comply with this Section 4.

5. **COOKIES, PIXELS, AND OTHER TECHNOLOGIES**

Our Website uses monitoring technologies including: 

* **Cookies.** A cookie is a piece of information that a website stores on a user’s computer, and that the user’s browser provides to the website each time the user submits a query to the website using that browser. When you access our Website, we place cookies on your computer. Some cookies allow us to make it easier for you to navigate our Sites, while others are used to enable a faster log-in process or to allow us to track your activities on our Sites. There are two types of cookies: session and persistent cookies.
* **Pixel Tags**. Pixel tags (sometime called web beacons or clear GIFs) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies. While cookies are stored locally on your device, pixel tags are embedded invisibly within web pages and online content. We may use these, in connection with our Services to, among other things, track the activities of users and help us manage content and compile usage statistics. 

6. **ANALYTICS**

We use the information we receive from third parties such as Google Analytics based on our legitimate interests in promoting and improving the Services and our services. You can download the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on to prevent your information from being used by Google Analytics at [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). Note that we do not combine the information collected through the use of third-party tools with any Personal Information collected from you. You may remove Cookies by following the instructions on your device governing the setting of your preferences. Our Cookies do not enable any access to or inspection of other information on your device. If you wish to be notified of when Cookies are placed on your device, you may set your web browser to provide such notices.

These are some of the tools used in our Products and/or Website:

* **Hotjar.** We use [Hotjar](https://www.hotjar.com/) in order to better understand our users’ needs and to optimize our service and user experience. Hotjar is a technology service that helps us better understand our users’ experience (e.g., how much time they spend on which pages, which links they choose to click, what users do and do not like, etc.) and this enables us to build and maintain our service with user feedback. Hotjar uses cookies and other technologies to collect data on our users’ behavior and their devices (in particular, device IP address (captured and stored only in anonymized form), device screen size, device type (unique device identifiers), browser information, geographic location (country only), preferred language used to display our website). Hotjar stores this information in a pseudonymized user profile. Neither Hotjar nor we will ever use this information to identify individual users or to match it with further data on an individual user. For further details, please see Hotjar’s privacy policy by clicking on [this link](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/privacy) ([https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/privacy/](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/privacy/)).
    * You can opt out of the creation of a user profile, Hotjar’s storing of data about your usage of our site and Hotjar’s use of tracking cookies on other websites, by following this [opt-out link](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/compliance/opt-out) ([https://www.hotjar.com/policies/do-not-track/](https://www.hotjar.com/policies/do-not-track/)).
* **Taboola.** Our Website uses technologies from Taboola Inc. (28 West 23rd St. 5th Fl, New York, NY 10010, [www.taboola.com](http://www.taboola.com/), “Taboola”). Taboola uses Cookies that determine how you navigate our Website, which of our pages you visit, and to determine what content and video services you use. The Cookie enables us to create pseudonymous user profiles by collecting device-related data as well as log data, and to recommend content that suits your personal interests, so that we can design our offer individually for you. These usage profiles are not merged with data about the bearer of the pseudonym and do not allow us to draw any conclusions about the data subject. For more information about Taboola and the ability to disable the Taboola Cookie, visit [https://www.taboola.com/privacy-policy](https://www.taboola.com/privacy-policy).
* **Facebook Pixel.** Our website measures conversions using visitor action pixels from Facebook Inc. (1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA, “Facebook”).
    * These allow the behavior of site visitors to be tracked after they click on a Facebook ad to reach the provider’s website, allowing an analysis of the effectiveness of Facebook advertisements for statistical and market research purposes and their future optimization.
    * The data collected is anonymous to us as operators of this website and we cannot use it to draw any conclusions about our users’ identities. However, the data are stored and processed by Facebook, which may make a connection to your Facebook profile, and which may use the data for its own advertising purposes, as stipulated in the Facebook privacy policy. This will allow Facebook to display ads both on Facebook and on third-party sites. We have no control over how this data is used.  See Facebook’s privacy policy to learn more about protecting your privacy: [https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/).
    * You can deactivate the Facebook custom audiences remarketing feature in the Ads Settings section at [https://www.facebook.com/ads/preferences/?entry\_product=ad\_settings\_screen.](https://www.facebook.com/ads/preferences/?entry_product=ad_settings_screen.)
* **Firebase.** We use Firebase ([https://firebase.google.com/](https://firebase.google.com/)) for user registration and authentication, for users who decide to create accounts and provide their email address and create passwords for that purpose. For further details, please see Firebase’s privacy policy by following [this link](https://firebase.google.com/support/privacy#firebase_data_processing_and_security_terms): https://firebase.google.com/support/privacy#firebase\_data\_processing\_and\_security\_terms.
* **PayPal and Stripe.** We use PayPal ([https://www.paypal.com/](https://www.paypal.com/)) and Stripe ([https://stripe.com/](https://stripe.com/)) to facilitate secure electronic payment by users for features and services that are offered for a fee. For further details, please see PayPal’s privacy policy by clicking on [this link](https://www.paypal.com/en/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full): [https://www.paypal.com/us/legalhub/privacy-full](https://www.paypal.com/us/legalhub/privacy-full). Also see Stripe’s privacy policy by following [this link](https://stripe.com/privacy): https://stripe.com/privacy.
* **Google AdMob.** Our Product may serve third-party advertisements, delivered to you by Google. Google processes an advertising ID from the device on which ads are served to determine interests, demographics, and other data, which may be used to serve better targeted ads to the user via the Google Mobile Ads SDK. For further details, please see Google’s privacy policy by following [this link](https://policies.google.com/privacy) ([https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)). See also the AdMob policy at [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy). See the AdSense program policy at https://support.google.com/admob/answer/2753860#Interest\_based. You can learn more about how Google uses your information at www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/ (“How Google uses information from sites or apps that use our services”). 

7. **YOUR INFORMATION COLLECTION CHOICES**

**App Privacy Choices**

You may opt out of the automatic collection and sharing of de-identified information collected by our mobile apps as follows:

* **For the mobile app (Android):** You can opt out and stop the automated collection and sharing of your browsing data by opting out of the  Accessibility Permissions through settings. 
* **For the mobile app (iOS):** You can opt out and stop the automated collection and sharing of your browsing data by opting out of the VPN Permissions through settings     .     

Note that once you opt out or turn off the Accessibility/VPN Permissions, some or all of the Services provided by BlockSite will no longer be available.

**Browser Extension Privacy Choices**

You may opt out of the automatic collection and sharing of de-identified information collected by our browser extension as follows:

* You can opt out and stop the automated collection and sharing of your browsing data by opting out of the data collection through the extension settings. 

Note that once you opt out or turn off the permissions, some or all of the Services provided by BlockSite will no longer be available.

**Website Privacy** **Choices**

To the extent any cookies are deployed on the website, if you wish to prevent such cookies or third-party advertisers from tracking your activity on our Website or visits across multiple websites, there are resources you can use to disable cookies and opt out of interest-based advertising. Using the resources below does not mean you will no longer receive any advertising through our Website, Services, or on other websites. You may continue to receive advertisements, for example, based on the particular website that you are viewing (i.e., context     -based ads). Your opt-out may not be necessary if your browser is already configured to reject cookies.

* **Browser Solutions.** You can decide if and how your computer will accept cookies by configuring the preferences option within your web browser, using the instructions provided in your browser. If you choose to decline cookies, however, some of the functionality of this Website might be impaired. 
* **Industry Solutions.** Notwithstanding the above, visitors to our Website may follow the steps provided by initiatives that educate users on how to set tracking preferences for most online advertising tools, such as the Network Advertising Initiative ([https://thenai.org/about-online-advertising/](https://thenai.org/about-online-advertising/)) and the Digital Advertising Alliance ([https://digitaladvertisingalliance.org/](https://digitaladvertisingalliance.org/)).

In order to disable some cookies or otherwise adjust your cookie preferences, please adjust the settings on your browser. Please note that if you disable certain cookies on your browser, some parts of our Services may not fully work or may otherwise be limited or affected. If you use a new computer, upgrade, or change web browsers or take any action which results in the deletion of the “opt out” cookie, you will need to perform this opt-out process again upon any such change.

**Third-Party Websites and Services**

Our Services may recommend third-party websites which we determine may be of interest to you (“**Third-Party Sites**”). Additionally, there may be links on our Website to third-party websites and services (“**Third-Party Services**”). We do not have control over such Third-Party Sites or Third-Party Services. We are not responsible for their privacy practices or policies. We therefore recommend that you review the privacy policies of these Third-Party Sites and Third-Party Services before providing them with your Personal Information. We use Third-Party Services remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online. Third party vendors, including Google, may show our ads on sites across the Internet. By using the [Ads Settings](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated), visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads.

8. **HOW WE PROTECT AND STORE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

**Security**

We have implemented and maintain appropriate technical and organizational security measures, policies and procedures designed to reduce the risk of accidental destruction or loss, or the unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, disclosure or access to your personal information. Although we take the above measures to secure the Personal Information, we cannot guarantee the security of information transmitted through the internet. As the security of information depends in part on the security of the computer you use to communicate with us and the security you use to protect your user IDs and passwords, please take appropriate measures to protect this information.

**Retention of Your Personal Information**

We store your Personal Information for as long as is reasonably necessary for the purposes for which it was collected, as explained in this Privacy Policy. In some circumstances we may store your Personal Information for longer periods of time, including where we are permitted or required to do so in accordance with legal, regulatory, tax or accounting requirements, in the event of any legal complaints, or if we reasonably believe there is a prospect of litigation relating to your Personal Information or dealings. 

9. **USER RIGHTS**

Where provided under applicable law (e.g., within the European Union and United Kingdom), you may have the right:

* To confirm with us whether your Personal Information is processed, and if it is, to request access to the Personal Information processed, the purpose of the processing, and the recipients or categories of recipients of your Personal Information. 
* To rectify inaccurate or incomplete Personal Information concerning you. We encourage you to review your information on the BlockSite Services regularly to ensure that it is accurate and up to date. 
* In certain circumstances, to ask us to erase Personal Information concerning you (i.e., delete your Personal Information);
* To request that we restrict the processing of your Personal Information in certain circumstances.
* To object to the processing of your Personal Information, where we are relying on a legitimate interest for such processing.
* To object to us processing your Personal Information for direct marketing purposes.
* To receive your Personal Information in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format or ask that we transfer the Personal Information, to another organization. This right only applies if our lawful basis for such processing is your consent or a contract, we have entered into with you. 
* To withdraw your consent at any time, where we are relying on consent to process your Personal information. This will not affect the lawfulness of any processing carried out before you withdraw your consent. 

Note that where your Personal Information has been de-identified, we will not be able to identify you or comply with some of the rights mentioned above. These rights do not apply to de-identified information. Additionally, these rights are not absolute and may therefore be subject to applicable exceptions, such as the interest of other individuals, in order to preserve that information for anticipated litigation or demands from a regulator.

10. **DELETE DATA AND EXERCISE RIGHTS**

Please contact our Data Protection Officer at: [dpo@blocksite.co i](mailto:dpo@blocksite.co)f you would like to exercise any of the rights included in Section 10 above or Section 14 below. Note that we may request proof of your identity, and we reserve the right to charge a fee where permitted by law, such as in circumstances where your request is deemed to be excessive. You may have the right to lodge a complaint with a data protection authority, subject to applicable law (as is the case in the European Union and the UK). You can find information on the relevant EU data protection authorities [here](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/about-edpb/members_en#member-at) and the UK Information Commissioner’s Office [here](https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/contact-us-public/). 

If you would like to delete your Personal Information or data please do so by choosing one of the following options: 

* **Permanently delete your account:**

You can also choose to delete your account and the data associated with your account by visiting the account setting page [here](https://user.blocksite.co/settings/account) and clicking the “Delete My Account” button or by contacting support via our [online form](https://blocksite.co/support-requests) and selecting the “Account deletion” option.

* **Delete some or all of your data or information (including your Personal Information)**: 

Please email us at: [dpo@blocksite.co](mailto:dpo@blocksite.co) to request that we delete some or all of your data (including your Personal Information). 

11. **USE BY CHILDREN**

If you are considered a “child” or a “minor” in your jurisdiction you are prohibited from using the Services. In the event that we become aware that a child has provided any Personal Information to us, we will discard such information. If you have any reason to believe that a child has shared any Personal Information with us, please contact our Data Protection Officer at: dpo@blocksite.co. If you are under 18, please be sure to read this Privacy Policy with your parents or legal guardians and ask questions about things you do not understand.

12. **CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**

This Privacy Policy is current as of the Last Updated date set forth above. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please be sure to check back periodically. We will post any updates to Privacy Policy on the Website and BlockSite Apps. We will not make material changes to how we collect, use and disclose the Personal Information we have previously collected about you without prior notice.

13. **HOW TO CONTACT US**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or how we collect and use Personal Information, please contact us at: dpo@blocksite.co.

14. **ADDITIONAL PRIVACY INFORMATION FOR CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS**

This section of the Privacy Policy provides additional information for California residents and describes our information practices pursuant to applicable California privacy laws, including      the California Consumer Privacy Act, as amended by the California Privacy Rights Act of 2020 (the “**CCPA**”). To the extent you are a resident of California, and we collect “Personal Information” subject to CCPA, the following applies. 

This section does not address or apply to our handling of publicly available      information      or to Personal Information that is otherwise exempt under the CCPA. This section also does not address or apply to Personal Information we collect and process about BlockSite employees, personnel, and job applicants, which are subject to different privacy notices.

**Categories of Personal Information Collected and Disclosed**. While our processing of Personal Information varies based upon our relationship and interactions with you, the      table below identifies the categories of Personal Information we may collect about you (and may have collected in the prior 12 months), as defined by the CCPA, as well as the categories      of third parties to whom we disclosed Personal Information      for a business or commercial purpose.      

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| **Categories of Personal Information Collected** |     | **Categories of**      **Third-Party Disclosures** |
| Identifiers | Includes direct identifiers, such as name, alias, account number or unique personal identifier; email address,      and other contact information; IP address and other online identifiers. | Affiliates      Advisors and agentsAdvertising networksData analytics providersSocial networksRegulators, government entities, and law enforcement (if required to do so by law or court order)Others as required by law |
| Customer Records | Incudes information such as name, user ID, account name, contact information, and other similar information. | Affiliates      Advisors and agentsRegulators, government entities, and law enforcement (if required to do so by law or court order)Others as required by law |
| Internet and Electronic Network Activity Information | Includes browsing history, clickstream data, search history, and information regarding interactions with our website and services, advertisements, or emails, including other usage data related to your use of any of our services or other similar online services. | Affiliates      Advisors and agentsRegulators, government entities, and law enforcement (if required to do so by law or court order)Others as required by law |
| Commercial Information | Includes records of products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or use histories or tendencies. | Affiliates            Advisors and agentsRegulators, government entities, and law enforcement (if required to do so by law or court order)Others as required by law |
| Location Data | Such as general location information about a particular individual or device. | Affiliates            Advisors and agentsRegulators, government entities, and law enforcement (if required to do so by law or court order)Others as required by law |
| Audio, Video, and other Electronic Data | Includes audio, electronic, visual      and call recordings (e.g., of customer support calls). | Affiliates           Advisors and agentsRegulators, government entities, and law enforcement (if required to do so by law or court order)Others as required by law |

**Sources of Personal Information**. We generally collect Personal Information from the following categories of sources: directly and indirectly from you; affiliates     ; business partners; vendors and service providers     ; operations systems and platforms, and marketing and data analytics providers.

**Purposes of Collection, Use, and Disclosure**. As described above in Section 2. How We Use Personal Information and Section 3. How We Share Personal Information, in general, we may collect, use, disclose and otherwise process the above personal information for the following business or commercial purposes and as otherwise directed or consented to by you:

* Operating Services and providing related support
* Analytics and improvement
* Marketing, advertising, and campaign management
* Security and protection of rights
* Compliance and legal process
* Business transfers
* Market intelligence or analytics services of our affiliates     
* Provision of Services by us and by our service providers, processors, and vendors.

**Retention**. We retain the personal information we collect only as reasonably necessary for the purposes described above or otherwise disclosed to you at the time of collection. For example, we will retain your account information for as long as you have an active account with us and additional information as necessary to comply with our legal, tax, accounting and recordkeeping obligations, to provide you with the services you have requested, as well as an additional period of time as necessary to protect, defend or establish our rights, defend against potential claims, and comply with our legal obligations. 

**Sales and Sharing of Personal Information**. CCPA defines a “sale” as disclosing or making Personal Information available to a third party in exchange for monetary or other valuable consideration. CCPA also defines “sharing” as disclosing or making available Personal Information to a third party for purposes of cross-context behavioral advertising. 

While we do not disclose Personal Information to third parties in exchange for monetary compensation, we may “sell” or “share” (as such terms are defined under the CCPA) the following categories of Personal Information in the following limited circumstances: 

* **Identifiers**: 

We may “sell” or “share” Identifiers with (1) social networks to enable you to login to the Services using your social network credentials and (2) affiliates in order to provide and improve the Services.

* **Internet and electronic network activity information**:

We may “Sell” or “Share” internet and electronic network activity information with (1) third-party ad networks on the BlockSite website to improve and evaluate our advertising campaigns and better reach customers and prospective customers with more relevant ads and content; (2) data analytics providers to monitor, audit, and analyze trends, usage, and activities in connection with our Services and advertisements; and (3) affiliates to provide and improve the Services. You can adjust your cookie preferences on the Website to block the collection of certain internet and electronic network activity information (_i.e_., you can opt out of the Sharing/Sale of your Personal Information).

We do not sell or share sensitive Personal Information, nor do we sell or share any Personal Information about individuals who we know are under sixteen (16) years old.      

**Your California Privacy Rights**. The CCPA provides California residents with specific rights regarding their Personal Information. If you are a California resident, subject to certain conditions and exceptions, you may have the following rights to your Personal Information: 

* **Right to Know:** With respect to the Personal Information we have collected about you in the prior 12 months, you have the right to request: (i) the categories of Personal Information about you we have collected; (ii) the sources from which we have collected that Personal Information; (iii) our business or commercial purposes for collecting, selling, or sharing that Personal Information; (iv) the categories of third parties to whom we have disclosed that Personal Information; and (v) a copy of the specific pieces of your Personal Information we have collected.
* **Right to Correct:** You have the right to request that we correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information.
* **Right to Delete:** Subject to certain conditions and exceptions, you may have the right to request deletion of Personal Information that we have collected about you. 
* **Right to Opt-Out of Sale/Sharing:** You may have the right to opt-out of the “sale” or “sharing” of your Personal Information. 
* **Right to Limit Use and Disclosure**: You have the right to limit use and disclosure of your sensitive Personal Information. However, we do not collect, use, or disclose Sensitive Personal Information; thus, this right is not available to California residents.
* **Right to Non-Discrimination:** We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of the rights described in this section.

**Authorized Agent:** You may also designate someone as an authorized agent to submit requests and act on your behalf. Authorized agents will be required to provide proof of their authorization in their first communication with us, and we may also require that the relevant consumer directly verify their identity and the authority of the authorized agent.

**Submitting CCPA Requests**. California residents      may exercise the      rights described above via the methods described below     : 

* **Right to Know, Delete, and Correct**: California residents may submit CCPA requests to access/know, delete, and correct Personal Information by contacting us at [dpo@blocksite.co](mailto:dpo@blocksite.co). You can also choose to delete your account and the data associated with your account by visiting the account setting page [here](https://user.blocksite.co/settings/account) and clicking the “Delete My Account” button or by contacting support via our [online form](https://blocksite.co/support-requests) and selecting the “Account deletion” option.

When you submit a request, we will take steps to verify your identity and request by matching the information provided by you with the information we have in our records. In some cases, we may request additional information in order to verify your identity, or where necessary to process your request. If we are unable to verify your identity after a good faith attempt, we may deny the request and, if so, will explain the basis for the denial.

You may also designate someone as an authorized agent to submit requests and act on your behalf. Authorized agents will be required to provide proof of their authorization in their first communication with us, and we may also require that the relevant consumer directly verify their identity and the authority of the authorized agent.

* **Right to Opt-Out of Sale/Sharing**:

**For the mobile app (Android):** You can opt out of the sale/sharing of your personal information by clicking on the “Your Privacy Choices” link in the mobile app menu and configuring the settings or by opting out of the  Accessibility Permissions through settings.

**For the mobile app (iOS):** You can opt out of the sale/sharing of your personal information by clicking on the “Your Privacy Choices” link in the mobile app menu and configuring the settings or by opting out of the  VPN Permissions through settings.

**Browser Extension**: You can opt out of the sale/sharing of your personal information by clicking on the “Your Privacy Choices” link in the “Settings” menu and turning off the automated collection of your browsing data or by opting out of the data collection through the extension settings.

**Website**. You can opt out of the sale/sharing of your personal information by clicking on the “Your Privacy Choices” link on the bottom of the Website homepage and opting out of targeting cookies, to the extent collected.

If you have any questions about our privacy practices or this Privacy Policy, please contact us as noted above in **Section 12. How to Contact Us.**

Our Website uses cookies
------------------------

We Use Cookies for various purposes including analytics, personalized content and ads. By continuing to browse this site, you agree to our use of cookies as described in our [Privacy Policy](https://blocksite.co/privacy)

OK, GOT IT

Take control of your time. Block distracting apps and sites. Make productivity your priority

[

](https://www.facebook.com/BlockSite.co/)[

](https://twitter.com/BlockSite_)[

](https://www.linkedin.com/company/blocksite/)[

](https://www.instagram.com/blocksite_official/)

Product

Connect

Our Policies

Resources

**Enjoy exclusive offers and updates**  
Ensure that you never miss out on our promotions and special feature releases

© All rights reserved for BlockSite 2024

Available On

[Take Back Your Focus. Discover and Block Your Biggest Digital Distractions.

Reveal My Distractions

Reveal My Distractions](https://user.blocksite.co/suggestions-lp?utm_source=Privacy%20Policy%20Website%20and%20App)
